{
    "subject": "resource/Pennsylvania",
    "predicate": "property/timezone",
    "object": "resource/Eastern_Time_Zone",
    "human_readable": "Pennsylvania's timezone is Eastern Time Zone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9829896688461304,
            "question": "Is Pennsylvania's timezone Central or Eastern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9092345833778381,
            "question": "What timezone is Pennsylvania in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8063254356384277,
            "question": "Which major US time zone includes Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6212494969367981,
            "question": "What time zone do people living in Pennsylvania use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5691776871681213,
            "question": "What time zone does Pennsylvania share with states like New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5454805493354797,
            "question": "Can you name any other states that use the Eastern Time Zone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4799267053604126,
            "question": "What time zone would you need to adjust to when traveling from Pennsylvania to California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47432711720466614,
            "question": "If it's 7:00 AM in Pennsylvania, what time is it in California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4426843523979187,
            "question": "How many hours ahead of Eastern Time is Central Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32183024287223816,
            "question": "When it's noon in Philadelphia, what time is it in New York City?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pennsylvania's timezone is Eastern Time Zone.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7937_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many hours ahead of Eastern Time is Central Time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7937_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If it's 7:00 AM in Pennsylvania, what time is it in California?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7937_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What time zone would you need to adjust to when traveling from Pennsylvania to California?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7937_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7937_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the JSON response based on the context information:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all documents provided mention that locations in Pennsylvania (e.g., Penn, Philadelphia, Central, Atlantic, Pittsburgh) are officially in the Eastern Time Zone. Therefore, it can be concluded that Pennsylvania's timezone is indeed the Eastern Time Zone."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents repeatedly confirms that various locations in Pennsylvania, including specific cities and regions, are indeed in the Eastern Time Zone. This supports the statement that \"Pennsylvania's timezone is Eastern Time Zone.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}